Guide to the Duplex Advertising Company. Billboard Images and Records, 1964-1993 and undated RL.00339
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Negatives Series, 1978-1985 and undated
  - Negatives from binder, undated (Box 12)
    - Oliver Brothers, pages 2, 83 (Box 12)
    - Ortegas, page 33 (Box 12)
    - Outlet Malls, page 45 (Box 12)
    - P & K Hardware, pages 120, 137 (Box 12)
    - Pace, page 53 (Box 12)
    - Pagel's Jewelers, pages 32, 36, 38 (Box 12)
    - Palm Harbor Homes, page 121 (Box 12)
    - Partner, page 51 (Box 12)
    - Pavelka's Yamaha, pages 32, 37 (Box 12)
    - Pearl Beer, pages 5, 69, 97, 101, 106, 138 (Box 12)
    - Pearl Light, pages 113, 114, 135 (Box 12)
    - Peppermint Patti's Clothing, page 16 (Box 12)
    - Pepsi, pages 117, 147 (Box 12)
    - Personnel Pool, page 143 (Box 12)
    - Photo Unlimited, page 59 (Box 12)
    - Photographics Unlimited, pages 19, 37, 93 (Box 12)
    - Picadilly, page 4 (Box 12)
    - Pioneer Baking Mix, page 16 (Box 12)
    - Plants and Things, pages 37, 59 (Box 12)
    - Plymouth, page 145 (Box 12)
    - Poboril Body Shop, page 40 (Box 12)
    - Prairie Ship Liberty, page 63 (Box 12)
    - Prather Appliances, pages 72, 83 (Box 12)
    - Precision Spas, pages 87, 89, 93 (Box 12)
    - Public Schol Week, page 17 (Box 12)
    - Putt-Putt, page 133 (Box 12)
    - Q 106, pages 18, 41, 63, 122, 125, 129, 131, 143, 146 (Box 12)
    - Quail Creek, pages 36, 58, 62 (Box 12)
    - Quail Creek Homes, pages 17, 84 (Box 12)
    - Quality Tire, pages 97, 99, 118, 119 (Box 12)
    - Quarterback Club, page 45 (Box 12)
    - Radisson Inn, pages 121, 122, 143 (Box 12)
    - Raid, page 5 (Box 12)
    - Railroad and Pioneer, page 31 (Box 12)
    - Raintree Inn, page 89 (Box 12)
    - Ralph Wilson Youth Clubs, pages 137, 138 (Box 12)
    - Ramada Inn, pages 115, 118, 131, 141 (Box 12)
    - Ranch House, page 94 (Box 12)
    - Ray Heating and Air Conditioning, page 72 (Box 12)
    - Red Wing Shoes, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Re-elect Cliff Jones, page 127 (Box 12)
    - Re-elect Grant Jones, page 129 (Box 12)
    - Rehab Telethon 1988, page 119 (Box 12)
    - Renegade, pages 98, 101, 104-106 (Box 12)
    - Restaurant Association, page 14 (Box 12)
    - Reveille Homes, pages 105, 112 (Box 12)
    - Richard's, pages 85, 89 (Box 12)
    - Richard's Memorial Hospital, pages 62, 78, 90 (Box 12)
    - Richland, page 43 (Box 12)
    - Richland Cigarettes, pages 42, 120, 129 (Box 12)
    - Richman's Carpets and Floors, page 133 (Box 12)
    - Rio Development, pages 34, 63, 73, 78 (Box 12)
    - Rio-Delta, page 12 (Box 12)
    - River Forests, page 61 (Box 12)
    - Rockdale, page 143 (Box 12)
    - Rockdale Bank, page 107 (Box 12)
    - Rockdale Ford, pages 80, 110 (Box 12)
    - Rockdale Inn, page 107 (Box 12)
    - Rodeway Inn, pages 98, 105, 107, 143 (Box 12)
    - Round Rock's, page 34 (Box 12)
    - RR Furniture, page 64 (Box 12)
    - RR West, page 104 (Box 12)
    - Rudy Mikeska's BBQ, pages 8, 34 (Box 12)
    - Russell's, pages 75, 141 (Box 12)
    - Russell's Cars, page 85 (Box 12)
    - RV Show, pages 92, 94 (Box 12)
    - S & C, pages 92, 99, 102, 104, 123, 137, 140, 146, 149 (Box 12)
    - Safeway, pages 39, 42, 46 (Box 12)
    - Salado First National Bank, page 118 (Box 12)
    - Salado Glenn Hodge, page 118 (Box 12)
    - Salem, pages 46, 52, 130, 51 (Box 12)
    - Satin Cigarettes, page 20 (Box 12)
    - Say Yes to Life, page 147 (Box 12)
    - Schlitz, pages 8, 51 (Box 12)
    - Schlotsky's, pages 38, 69, 99, 103, 111, 116, 119, 126, 148 (Box 12)
    - Scott & White, pages 20, 65, 78, 87, 133 (Box 12)
    - Scottish Inn, pages 33, 34 (Box 12)
    - Sea World, pages 125, 129, 145 (Box 12)
    - Sertoma, page 57 (Box 12)
    - Sesquicentennial, pages 32, 35, 58 (Box 12)
    - Sharp's, page 46 (Box 12)
    - Sheffield Funeral Homes, page 145 (Box 12)
    - Shell, pages 15, 44, 64, 76, 93 (Box 12)
    - Sidles, page 117 (Box 12)
    - Silver Bullet, page 137 (Box 12)
    - Slice, pages 67-69 (Box 12)
    - Smitty's, page 108 (Box 12)
    - Smorgasbord, pages 87, 96, 115, 117, 119, 142 (Box 12)
    - Sonic, page 121 (Box 12)
    - Southern Baptist, pages 32, 59, 60 (Box 12)
    - Southport Mobile Homes, pages 53, 54 (Box 12)
    - Southwest Travel Center, pages 15, 17 (Box 12)
    - Spaghetti Supper, page 19 (Box 12)
    - Stacy E., page 63 (Box 12)
    - Stagecoach, pages 3, 36 (Box 12)
    - Stagecoach Inn, page 39, 145 (Box 12)
    - Steak House, pages 116, 119 (Box 12)
    - Sterling, pages 42, 45 (Box 12)
    - Stewart, Inc., page 44 (Box 12)
    - Stewart Ins, page 60 (Box 12)
    - Stewarts, page 42 (Box 12)
    - Sticker Station, page 124 (Box 12)
    - Stockton, page 83 (Box 12)
    - Stockton Real Estate, page 41 (Box 12)
    - Stratford House Inn, pages 38, 47 (Box 12)
    - Stroh's, page 128 (Box 12)
    - Supercuts, page 71 (Box 12)
    - Suzuki, pages 12, 52 (Box 12)
    - SW Maternity Center, page 49 (Box 12)
    - Taco, page 67 (Box 12)
    - Taco Bell, pages 1, 3, 4, 8, 32, 54, 55, 82, 84 (Box 12)
    - Take 1 Video, pages 124-126, 129, 132, 146 (Box 12)
    - Tarpley's, page 84 (Box 12)
    - Tarpley's Electronics, page 92 (Box 12)
    - Taste of Central Texas, page 126 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, pages 130, 131 (Box 12)
    - Taylor Properties, pages 62, 78, 82 (Box 12)
    - TCT, pages 55, 97 (Box 12)
    - Teacher, page 110 (Box 12)
    - Teal's Exxon, pages 59, 61 (Box 12)
    - Temple, page 148 (Box 12)
    - Temple Bond Election, page 47 (Box 12)
    - Temple Civic Theater, pages 41, 117 (Box 12)
    - Temple Daily Telegram, pages 126, 129, 130, 132, 136 (Box 12)
    - Temple DT Association, page 89 (Box 12)
    - Temple Economic Development, page 59 (Box 12)
    - Temple Glass, page 61 (Box 12)
    - Temple High School, page 20 (Box 12)
    - Temple Informed Parents, page 20 (Box 12)
    - Temple Laundry, page 107 (Box 12)
    - Temple Laundry and Cleaners, page 128 (Box 12)
    - Temple Mall, pages 4, 30, 46, 67, 76, 77, 94, 144 (Box 12)
    - Temple National, page 55 (Box 12)
    - Temple Police, page 146 (Box 12)
    - Temple Suzuki, page 50 (Box 12)
    - Temple Telephone Directory, pages 38, 39 (Box 12)
    - Temple Wildcats, pages 126, 128 (Box 12)
    - Texaco, pages 71, 132, 133 (Box 12)
    - Texana, pages 84, 86 (Box 12)
    - Texana Bank, page 98 (Box 12)
    - Texana National Bank, pages 15a, 40, 44, 92 (Box 12)
    - Texas American Bank, page 111 (Box 12)
    - Texas Bank, pages 12, 49, 125, 126, 128, 132, 138, 143 (Box 12)
    - Texas Best Trucks, pages 46, 47, 83 (Box 12)
    - Texas Health, pages 99, 107 (Box 12)
    - Texas Inn, pages 88, 144 (Box 12)
    - Texas Premier, page 67 (Box 12)
    - Texas Restaurant Association, pages 3, 41 (Box 12)
    - Texas Safari, page 33 (Box 12)
    - Texas Sesquicentennial, page 48 (Box 12)
    - Texas Train, pages 44, 45 (Box 12)
    - Texas Train Festival, page 144 (Box 12)
    - Texas Village, pages 102, 113 (Box 12)
    - The Alternativ, pages 49, 50, 52 (Box 12)
    - The Mom's Shop, page 136 (Box 12)
    - Thrifty Nickel, pages 127, 134 (Box 12)
    - TJC, pages 87, 93, 95, 100, 102, 110, 131, 143 (Box 12)
    - TRA, page 44 (Box 12)
    - Traffic Tickets, page 125 (Box 12)
    - Trail's Inn, pages 101, 118, 119 (Box 12)
    - Train Festival, pages 73, 74, 76 (Box 12)
    - Tranum, page 87 (Box 12)
    - Tranum Buick, page 116 (Box 12)
    - Tranum Trades, page 133 (Box 12)
    - Tranum's, page 121 (Box 12)
    - Tranum-Hundley, page 9 (Box 12)
    - Tray International, page 124 (Box 12)
    - Tri-City, page 112 (Box 12)
    - Triple D, page 556 (Box 12)
    - Triple O, page 36 (Box 12)
    - Tripled, page 30 (Box 12)
    - Tri-Star, page 94 (Box 12)
    - Trucker's Rest, page 44 (Box 12)
    - Twin Caboose, page 52 (Box 12)
    - TX Best Trucks, page 59 (Box 12)
    - TX Village, page 101 (Box 12)
    - UMHB, page 79 (Box 12)
    - United Methodist Church, pages 95, 112, 136, 142, 149 (Box 12)
    - United Oil, page 93 (Box 12)
    - Universal Cleaning, pages 95, 119 (Box 12)
    - University Savings, page 34 (Box 12)
    - Varsity Motel, page 9 (Box 12)
    - Village Lamplighter, page 99 (Box 12)
    - Vocational Education, page 85 (Box 12)
    - Waco Boat Show, page 82 (Box 12)
    - Walberg Mercantile, page 64 (Box 12)
    - Walberg Restaurant, page 109 (Box 12)
    - Warehouse, page 83 (Box 12)
    - Water and Alcohol Don't Mix, page 131 (Box 12)
    - Weatherall, page 47 (Box 12)
    - Webb Drugs, pages 58, 84 (Box 12)
    - Welcome to Belton, pages 21, 36, 42 (Box 12)
    - Wendland Feed, pages 128, 140 (Box 12)
    - Wendland Fuel, page 122 (Box 12)
    - Wendland's, page 2, 80, 94, 103 (Box 12)
    - Wendy's, pages 5, 8, 12, 41, 42, 85 (Box 12)
    - Western Village, pages 54, 103 (Box 12)
    - Westlake, page 38 (Box 12)
    - Whataburger, pages 15a, 98, 118 (Box 12)
    - Wheeler's, pages 38, 42, 44, 48, 58, 60 (Box 12)
    - White Mountain Beer, page 134 (Box 12)
    - Whited Oil, page 76 (Box 12)
    - Whitfield, page 113 (Box 12)
    - Whitfield Photography, pages 136, 137, 140 (Box 12)
    - Wildcat, page 94 (Box 12)
    - Wildflower Capitol, page 126 (Box 12)
    - Wildflower Real Estate, page 127 (Box 12)
    - Williams County Equipment, pages 120, 130, 139, 141, 148, 149 (Box 12)
    - Windowsmith, pages 72, 95 (Box 12)
    - Winkler's, page 123 (Box 12)
    - Winston, pages 53, 67 (Box 12)
    - Wok's, page 130 (Box 12)
    - Wood Co., page 113 (Box 12)
    - Yellow Rows of Texas (Corona beer), page 138 (Box 12)
    - Young Pontiac, pages 63, 64, 73, 78 (Box 12)
    - Yowell's, page 38 (Box 12)
    - Yowell's Best, page 39 (Box 12)
    - Yowell's Boat Yard, page 68 (Box 12)
    - Zenith Cleaners, pages 104, 111 (Box 12)